{
    "subject": "resource/The_Smiling_Lieutenant",
    "predicate": "ontology/basedOn",
    "object": "resource/Hans_M\u00fcller-Einigen",
    "human_readable": "The Smiling Lieutenant is based on Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8092529773712158,
            "question": "Who is Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7954084873199463,
            "question": "What kind of story is 'The Smiling Lieutenant' based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7638041973114014,
            "question": "Is there a movie or adaptation based on 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7591371536254883,
            "question": "Who created the character Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6881973743438721,
            "question": "What is the name of the book or story that Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen is based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.652134358882904,
            "question": "Is there a real person behind 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6284594535827637,
            "question": "What is the genre of 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6123927235603333,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the character Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5852426886558533,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen and fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.575157105922699,
            "question": "What makes 'The Smiling Lieutenant' unique?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Smiling Lieutenant is based on Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7615_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen and fiction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7615_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the character Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7615_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7615_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7615_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my evaluation:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen as the source or inspiration for The Smiling Lieutenant. Instead, it is mentioned that the film was based on an Oscar Straus opretta and a German novel by Hans Muller (not Einigen)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, \"The Smiling Lieutenant\" is adapted from \"The Waltz Dream\" by Oscar Straus and a German novel by Hans Muller. There is no mention of it being based on Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen, thus the statement is not supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention or suggest that \"The Smiling Lieutenant\" (1931) is based on Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen. Instead, it states that the movie was based on an Oscar Straus operetta and a German novel.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state the film is based on Oscar Straus' operetta \"The Waltz Dream\" and Hans Muller's novel \"Nux der Prinzgemahl\".",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided does not mention Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen as the basis for the film, instead stating that \"The Smiling Lieutenant\" was adapted from an Oscar Straus opretta and based on a German novel.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the film is based on an Oscar Straus opretta and a German novel, not Hans M\u00fcller-Einigen.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}